Dan Rescigno

Red Bank, New Jersey, United States



rescigno.d@protonmail.com



linkedin.com/in/drescigno

Summary

Skilled Senior Consultant specializing in Clinical Operations. I strategically partner with Pharmaceutical Companies, Biotechs, CROs, Med-Device Companies, and Consultancies to assist in building out successful teams and functions. I also work exclusively with top talent within my own professional network.

Experience



Senior Consultant | Clinical Operations | North America

Investigo

Feb 2022 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Consultant | Regulatory Affairs | North America

Barrington James

Apr 2019 - Feb 2022 (2 years 11 months)

Strategic Account Manager | Major Accounts | Global

EcoTech Solutions

Jul 2016 - Apr 2019 (2 years 10 months)

Education



Monmouth University

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Business, Management, Marketing, and Related Support Services

Skills

Sales • Sales Process • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Recruiting • Customer Service • Social Media • Negotiation • Persuasive Speaker • Full-Stack Development • JavaScript